[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "What can you tell me about the subway, about power and about when New York will be back on its feet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Well, you know, that's a question that a lot of people are asking.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "How are these generators, both at NYU and Bellevue, the backup generators, why are they failing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Well, let me put it to you like this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NYU"], "LOCATION": ["Bellevue"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "How are things where you are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, the devastation in the southern parts of our state, you know, demand our attention, our compassion and our prayer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "EX", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "CC", "RBR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "And maybe fully reopened within the next day or so, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "You know, we -- yes, first of all, we are happy that it is open and there will be more and more activity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Manhattan"]}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Where were you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I was in my apartment on the west side of Manhattan here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "What is wrong with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "I was looking at that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ali Velshi"]}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", ":", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 184, "question": "What did he do here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Well, did I say they want to kill Ali Velshi but they -- yes, Ali -- when I saw that --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "If it saves one life, isn't it worth it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Well, yes, but there's a lot of things you could do on CNN to save many lives.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Now why is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "It's just because there's so much going on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Did you buy it or is there a more cynical, political reasoning behind what is going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, I'm -- firstly, I'm not a cynic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Like this (INAUDIBLE), whichever way you dress this up, divorcing it from the storm, this cannot help Mitt Romney can it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "But you could say by next Tuesday, if there are million so people still without power, feeling angry, you could get a protest vote, couldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "RB", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "First of all, I don't think it's about Mitt Romney not being able to get on television.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Tuesday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VB", "POS", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "How could this happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Well, first of all, let's be clear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "That is part of your job, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "It is very easy to make that judgement from a ring side seat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Michael, what do you think of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "You make valid points.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mayor Bloomberg"]}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Could it be that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I will answer the way that Mayor Bloomberg answered this afternoon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "From a meteorological point of view, is there any other explanation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "It is the prime suspect.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Do you believe the science is now incontrovertible?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Absolutely, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam"]}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "And when you hear mainly Republicans, it must be said, say the science is just a load of bunk, what do you say to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "These are the same people that say that Adam and Eve road on dinosaurs 6,000 years ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "National Guard", "National Guard"], "TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "RBR", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Is that what you are hearing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Well, Piers, the news is much more encouraging today than when I talked to you last night because what we have found is this, the National Guard has arrived, 45 members of the National Guard with 18 vehicles.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "But when these things happen, it really is inspiring to see how people react, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Was that his name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121031pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Were they prepared enough for this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Well, they weren't prepared, but only in the sense that they haven't accepted that we are going to have more and more of this because of the climate change.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]